/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/ANIMAL	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/GAME
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:prices:<nsubj>:drop:<-advcl>:expand:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PLANT	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-prep>:like:cans:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:estimated:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:Journal:<prep>:in:letter:<nsubj>:notes:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/HOSPITAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-det>:authors:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:three:<-vmod>:attending:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:disk:<nsubj>:combines:<-dobj>:animation:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:from:FAX:<nsubj>:begins:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PLANT#/ANIMAL	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:be:<-xcomp>:subsidizing:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:approval:<prep>:despite:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/FACILITY#/GPE#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:Ellis:<-dep>:estimates:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:before:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:before:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:owns:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dobj>:owns:<-rcmod>:Spiegel:<nsubj>:says:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/FACILITY#/GPE#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/LOCATION/REGION#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/LOCATION/REGION#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-amod>:drink:<appos>:Antarctica:<nsubjpass>:brought:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE#/LOCATION#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE#/LOCATION#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:Antarctica:<nsubjpass>:brought:<--prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:ale:<prep>:like:looks:<-conj>:and:tastes:<-prep>:like:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-prep>:like:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nsubj>:looks:<-prep>:like:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-prep>:like:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:,:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:asked:<nsubj>:``:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:,:<-appos>:,:<--prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<--prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:figures:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:city:<poss>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:encouraging:<ccomp>:says:<-nsubj>:Poppenberg:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:thought:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Savageau:<nsubj>:live:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Ana:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Ana:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Ana:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Ana:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Ana:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Ky.:<-conj>:and:Ana:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<poss>:income:<nsubj>:fell:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:Angeles-based:<amod>:Northrop:<-nsubj>:recorded:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:from:fell:<-advcl>:continues:<-conj>:and:produced:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<number>:[YYY]	/LANGUAGE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:Backlog:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:shares:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:raise:<-conj>:and:hold:<-dobj>:share:<-prep>:against:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:offered:<-dobj>:way:<-vmod>:break:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:put:<-prep>:by:act:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:machine:<dobj>:ban:<-prep>:because_of:fears:<-prep>:over:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dep>:sales:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<xcomp>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:producers:<nsubj>:processors:<-rcmod>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-vmod>:turning:<-prep>:into:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<conj>:or:powdered:<amod>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT	[XXX]:<prep>:instead_of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:bakers:<prep>:of:dozens:<nsubj>:say:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT
/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT	[XXX]:<vmod>:products:<nsubj>:lose:<-dobj>:zip:<-rcmod>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-dep>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:speed:<prep>:at:spin:<conj>:and:put:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:put:<-conj>:and:spin:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-prep>:at:spin:<-vmod>:break:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT
/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:idea:<-prep>:behind:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-prep>:about:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-prep>:about:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:King:<-dep>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:tall:<amod>:feet:<nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nsubj>:expensive:<advcl>:recover:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<amod>:eggs:<nsubj>:expensive:<advcl>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT	[XXX]:<dep>:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/FACILITY/HIGHWAY_STREET
/PLANT	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PLANT	[XXX]:<dobj>:pass:<-conj>:and:found:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT
/PRODUCT/WEAPON#/PRODUCT	[XXX]:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<advmod>:has:<-dobj>:potential:<-dep>:spread:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PLANT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:says:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-vmod>:broken:<-agent>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:protection:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:trying:<-xcomp>:make:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PLANT#/ANIMAL	[XXX]:<-dobj>:make:<-prep>:at:expense:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:was:<-prep>:in:charge:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/GAME	[XXX]:<-dobj>:complaints[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:letter:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dep>:went:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:based:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:based:<-rcmod>:Maynard:<nsubj>:enlisted:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-advcl>:took:<-prep>:on:floor:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-xcomp>:get:<-vmod>:examine:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:called:<-dobj>:method:<-prepc>:for:breaking:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/EVENT	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<vmod>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Jersey:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Jersey:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Jersey:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE#/LOCATION#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE#/LOCATION#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<advmod>:far:<advmod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:outlawed:<-vmod>:citing:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:company:<nsubj>:filed:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:court:<-prep>:in:filed:<-prep>:against:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:company:<-vmod>:pay:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:says:<-ccomp>:pushed:<-prep>:into:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:fell:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:chew:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:of:evidence:<prep>:on:do:<-advmod>:at:<-dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:in:chanteuse:<prep>:as:[YYY]	/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:handles:<-advcl>:hearing:<-dobj>:way:<-rcmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:like:character:<-rcmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/GAME
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Boys:<prep>:about:nothing:<-conj>:and:nothing:<-prep>:about:[YYY]	/PERSON
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:with:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<det>:movies:<nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<parataxis>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:with:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:emerges:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/GAME	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:with:years:<prep>:for:working:<prepc>:after:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:Fassbinder:<prep>:with:years:<prep>:for:working:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:with:working:<-prep>:for:years:<-prep>:with:Fassbinder:<-appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Jeff:<appos>:brothers:<dobj>:cast:<-prep>:as:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<prep>:like:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:between:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dep>:possible:<-ccomp>:natural:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:had:<-xcomp>:make:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:brothers:<nsubj>:doing:<ccomp>:opens:<advcl>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:out_of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:brother:<-rcmod>:fancies:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:remember:<-conj>:and:shows:<-parataxis>:consoles:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<amod>:Bridges:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:include:<-dobj>:audition:<-vmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:girlfriend:<prep>:as:stint:<prep>:during:showed:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<amod>:promise:<dobj>:showed:<--prep>:on:show:<-dep>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:think:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:at:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:sang:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:on:trade:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<nsubj>:agreed:<-xcomp>:sell:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/SUBSTANCE
/PLANT#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-dobj>:sell:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PLANT#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<nsubj>:won:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<nsubj>:got:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:responsible:<-prep>:for:materials:<-rcmod>:include:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:composites:<-dobj>:include:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION/CONTINENT#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:S.p[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:auditors:<-vmod>:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/ORGANIZATION#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION#/ORGANIZATION/MUSEUM#/FACILITY/BUILDING
/FACILITY#/ORGANIZATION#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION#/ORGANIZATION/MUSEUM#/FACILITY/BUILDING	[XXX]:<-vmod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:retired:<vmod>:Kelley:<nsubjpass>:elected:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:Lang:<nsubjpass>:elected:<-prep>:to:post:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:remains:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:president:<ccomp>:remains:<--xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<--xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:succeeds:<-conj>:and:becomes:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:as:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Warren:<nsubjpass>:named:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:post:<nsubj>:vacant:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-pobj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:expecting:<-prep>:following:fall:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:banks:<prep>:at:yielding:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/EVENT	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:Litvack:<nsubj>:said:<-prep>:into:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:into:said:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Litvack:<-appos>:president:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:president:<-appos>:Litvack:<nsubj>:said:<--prep>:into:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/LANGUAGE
/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:marches:<prep>:of:features:<prep>:of:One:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/GAME
/GAME	[XXX]:<dep>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:resolution:<-vmod>:designating:<-prep>:as:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:Remembrance:<-prep>:of:Anniversary:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:on:approved:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<expl>:no:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:with:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:one:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/LOCATION/CONTINENT#/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/LOCATION/CONTINENT#/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:seeking:<-dobj>:help:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PRODUCT	[XXX]:<dep>:accept:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:one:<nsubj>:blames:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:effort:<dep>:notwithstanding:<prep>:lie:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/LOCATION/CONTINENT#/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/LOCATION/CONTINENT#/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:people:<prep>:of:majority:<prep>:of:faith:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-amod>:Turks:<-vmod>:arriving:<-prep>:as:refugees:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:tragedy:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:tragedy:<nsubjpass>:ignored:<-conj>:and:shuttled:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:we:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:at:improve:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<amod>:funds:<-rcmod>:allowed:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<appos>:Oakar:<nsubj>:wants:<-dep>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:build:<-dobj>:Rock:<-conj>:and:Hall:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:says:<-ccomp>:create:<-conj>:and:bring:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:says:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:implication:<-dep>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:with:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:'re:<-dep>:explain:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:toward:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<poss>:spending:<prep>:of:Much:<nsubj>:welfare:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:money:<nsubj>:trickle:<-conj>:and:free:<-vmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/LANGUAGE	[XXX]:<advmod>:suburban:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE#/LOCATION#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE#/LOCATION#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:reclaims:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:spends:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:at:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<prep>:into:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<advmod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:after:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:extent:<nsubj>:stemmed:<-prep>:from:years:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:parallel:<-prep>:after:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PLANT	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:is:<-advcl>:culminated:<-prep>:in:stop:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:assumption:<nsubj>:is:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<pobj>:enough:<advmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<-vmod>:craning:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION#/FACILITY/BUILDING
/FACILITY#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION#/FACILITY/BUILDING	[XXX]:<-prep>:at:craning:<-vmod>:economists:<nsubj>:claimed:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<-dep>:fellows:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:at:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dep>:Pollin:<-prep>:of:faculty:<-prep>:at:University:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<rcmod>:economists:<--dep>:fellows:<--prep>:in:Union:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:consequence:<-prep>:of:burden:<-appos>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:rates:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/PERSON	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:wage:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:readings:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:columnist:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:try:<-xcomp>:sell:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Texas:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Texas:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Texas:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:package:<nsubjpass>:comprised:<-prep>:of:properties:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:terms:<prep>:with:were:<-advcl>:compiled:<-prep>:by:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-prep>:by:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-dep>:$:<-vmod>:priced:<-agent>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:by:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<-dep>:$:<-vmod>:offered:<-agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:offering:<nsubjpass>:backed:<-agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<dep>:Kidder:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:offering:<nsubjpass>:backed:<-agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:offerings:<nsubj>:bring:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dep>:lire:<-prep>:via:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG#/WORK_OF_ART/PLAY
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Finance:<-dep>:units:<-prep>:via:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-dep>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dep>:francs:<-prep>:via:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:issue:<nsubjpass>:sold:<-prep>:through:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Goodfellow:<-rcmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-xcomp>:manage:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PLANT	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<dep>:company:<nsubj>:called:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:product:<nsubj>:based:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Mass[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<pobj>:by:<pcomp>:provided:<prep>:carry:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GAME	[XXX]:<prep>:through:[YYY]	/PLANT
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:at:manager:<appos>:Goodwin:<nsubj>:adapted:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:,:<agent>:new:<-xcomp>:developed:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:computer:<-prep>:to:Salton:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:operating:<ccomp>:says:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/EVENT	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:higher:<-dep>:ratio:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Golomb:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/LANGUAGE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:humans:<nsubj>:write:<-dobj>:abstracts:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<advmod>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<predet>:computers:<nsubj>:make:<ccomp>:says:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nn>:Digate:<-appos>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-vmod>:known:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<amod>:briefing:<-prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Inc.:<nsubj>:lost:<-xcomp>:involving:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:panel:<nsubj>:ordered:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dobj>:ordered:<-xcomp>:pay:<-prep>:to:Kelly:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:Newcomb:<prep>:to:bonuses:<prep>:in:awarded:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:at:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Liddle:<prep>:at:attorney:<-dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:lost:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:involving:<xcomp>:lost:<--parataxis>:paid:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-dobj>:dispute:<-prep>:between:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-appos>:unit:<-prep>:of:Sears:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PLANT#/ANIMAL	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-ccomp>:contributed:<-prep>:away_from:calls:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Wednesday:<tmod>:quiz:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:subcommittee:<conj>:and:Energy:<nsubj>:quiz:<--conj>:and:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:quiz:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Energy:<nsubj>:quiz:<---conj>:and:go:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-tmod>:go:<-prep>:before:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nsubj>:work:<-prep>:despite:fact:<-dep>:opposed:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO
/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:FALTERS:<-prep>:amid:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<xcomp>:cut:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:economic:<-dobj>:cut:<-xcomp>:force:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:rival:<-prep>:for:ineptitude:<-prepc>:in:forcing:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:rival:<--prep>:for:ineptitude:<--prepc>:in:forcing:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:officials:<nsubj>:fear:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:blamed:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:is:<-parataxis>:pushing:<-prep>:as:alternative:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<poss>:rejection:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:effort:<-vmod>:expedite:<-prepc>:by:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prepc>:by:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:Dole:<nsubj>:ridicules:<-dobj>:chief:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<acomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<mark>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Britain:<nsubj>:pull:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:frigates:<dobj>:build:<xcomp>:pull:<--parataxis>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/LOCATION/REGION#/GPE#/LOCATION
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:experts:<nsubj>:say:<-parataxis>:fear:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:EXPECT:<-xcomp>:solidify:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:like:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:administration:<nsubj>:like:<--parataxis>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<xcomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:coup:<prep>:of:wake:<prep>:in:appears:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/LAW	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<discourse>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/LANGUAGE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nn>:team:<prep>:in_addition_to:lined:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nn>:victor:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Vittoria:<-conj>:and:victor:<dep>:chairman:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:head:<conj>:and:victor:<dep>:chairman:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:chairman:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:chairman:<-dep>:victor:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:chairman:<--dep>:victor:<--conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:investor:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT	[XXX]:<dobj>:awarded:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:team:<prep>:by:appeal:<-vmod>:led:<-agent>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:official:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:spokesman:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Hurst:<nsubj>:writing:<-prep>:in:issue:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-nn>:Hurst:<nsubj>:writing:<--prep>:in:issue:<--prep>:of:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:loss:<nsubj>:is:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/PERSON#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<ccomp>:mean:<ccomp>:did:<advcl>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dep>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-dep>:School:<nsubj>:did:<advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<pobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GAME	[XXX]:<mark>:found:<advcl>:turned:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prepc>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Stanton:<--prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-det>:judge:<nsubj>:ruled:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT	[XXX]:<prep>:from:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Sommer:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:preserves:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<nn>:binge:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:prices:<nsubj>:jumped:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-ccomp>:bought:<-vmod>:bringing:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<tmod>:confirmed:<-advcl>:announced:<--ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:at:trading:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:sign:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<num>:sign:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:tons:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:oil:<prep>:of:sale:<dobj>:subsidize:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:subsidize:<-dobj>:sale:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<predet>:this[YYY]	/PLANT#/PRODUCT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:farmers:<nsubj>:used:<-vmod>:sell:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/PLANT#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<nn>:prices:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:claims:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:strengthened:<-prep>:during:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-prep>:during:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:are:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:fell:<-prep>:in:reaction:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/EVENT
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:purchasing:<dobj>:increased:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE
/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:mine:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:likelihood:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:prices:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<amod>:futures:<nsubj>:opened:<-prep>:following:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:epicenter:<-prep>:after:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:likely:<-xcomp>:filed:<-prep>:against:firms:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:have:<-advcl>:reach:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Drivon:<-appos>:president-elect:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:on:saw:<pcomp>:From:<dep>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nsubj>:points:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/FACILITY/HIGHWAY_STREET
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:Belli:<nsubj>:says:<-ccomp>:has:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/FACILITY/BUILDING
/FACILITY#/FACILITY/BUILDING	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:met:<ccomp>:prove:<advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Covert:<-appos>:lawyer:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:with:[YYY]	/EVENT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/FACILITY/BRIDGE#/FACILITY	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:association:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/FACILITY/BRIDGE#/FACILITY
/FACILITY/BRIDGE#/FACILITY	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:by:use:<-dep>:Sells:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:firm:<nsubj>:withdrew:<-conj>:and:joined:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Bullock:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:known:<-advcl>:added:<-dobj>:name:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Burton:<-appos>:professor:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL#/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL#/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:noted:<advcl>:hold:<ccomp>:said:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:believes:<-dobj>:action:<-prep>:by:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:committes:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<tmod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:say:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:work:<dobj>:keeping:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dep>:Touche:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:lose:<-prep>:for:audit:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/LOCATION/CONTINENT#/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:defection:<nsubj>:make:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Amhowitz:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:earthquake:<-conj>:and:devastation:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE
/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:devastation:<-conj>:and:earthquake:<prep>:of:wake:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-amod>:particularly:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/FACILITY#/ORGANIZATION#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION	[XXX]:<pobj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:planning:<-prep>:at:Co.:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:shoes:<prep>:such_as:supplies:<dobj>:keep:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:office:<-rcmod>:take:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<pobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:talking:<ccomp>:says:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:earthquake:<-conj>:and:fire:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<vmod>:lost:<-prep>:with:branches:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:president:<-conj>:and:security:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Corp.:<nsubj>:holds:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/FACILITY#/ORGANIZATION#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/FACILITY#/ORGANIZATION#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:threatened:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE
/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE	[XXX]:<dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<amod>:hours:<-nsubj>:ready:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE
/EVENT#/EVENT/HURRICANE	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<expl>:are:<ccomp>:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/ORGANIZATION#/FACILITY/ATTRACTION#/ORGANIZATION/MUSEUM#/FACILITY/BUILDING
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:cars:<nsubj>:float:<-advcl>:get:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Gaubert:<-rcmod>:wrested:<-agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO	[XXX]:<-pobj>:ruling:<-prep>:by:[YYY]	/EVENT#/LAW
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:into:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-rcmod>:chairman:<-conj>:and:stockholder:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:regulators:<prep>:of:control:<pobj>:under:<advcl>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:worth:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-xcomp>:wiping:<-dobj>:value:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:by:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:suit:<nsubjpass>:dismissed:<-prep>:under:[YYY]	/LAW
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:panel:<nsubj>:upheld:<-conj>:but:said:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/LAW
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-amod>:officials:<nsubj>:cause:<-dobj>:deterioration:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:depend:<-ccomp>:cause:<--dobj>:deterioration:<--prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:lawyer:<--appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:establish:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Union:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:'d:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/PLANT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:firing:<nsubj>:violated:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<prep>:in:pregnant:<ccomp>:told:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:hire:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:taped:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:taped:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PLANT#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:Aloe:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PLANT#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-vmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<advmod>:inflate:<-dobj>:price:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/FACILITY/BUILDING
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:through:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:pays:<-prep>:as:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:as:[YYY]	/PLANT
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Hart:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Hart:<nsubj>:says:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:received:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:Arlen:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:chairman:<-rcmod>:heard:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Browder:<prep>:of:firm:<-dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dep>:firm:<prep>:in:partners:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:partners:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<dep>:firm:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<num>:partners:<--prep>:in:firm:<--prep>:of:Browder:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Morris:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Morris:<-conj>:and:Morris:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Morris:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:partners:<-dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Morris:<--conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<--conj>:and:Morris:<--conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:outside:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dep>:Nixon:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Nixon:<-dep>:Doyle:<-vmod>:based:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Jr.:<conj>:and:office:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<conj>:and:Mayer:<nsubj>:added:<-prep>:to:office:<--conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:added:<--prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<rcmod>:Boorstyn:<nsubj>:joining:<-dobj>:McCutchen:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:McCutchen:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nn>:Co.:<poss>:report:<nsubj>:reinforcing:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:decline:<nsubj>:reflected:<ccomp>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:on:trading:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/LOCATION/RIVER#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<amod>:softness:<-prep>:in:advertising:<-prep>:at:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-det>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nsubj>:hard:<-xcomp>:do:<-advcl>:starts:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-nn>:chairman:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<appos>:``:<root>:.:<-root>:said:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:analyst:<-prep>:with:C.J[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PLANT	[XXX]:<ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:out:<ccomp>:said:<-nsubj>:Mateyo:<-appos>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:executive:<-prep>:of:Co.:<-appos>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:on:Volume:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PLANT
/PLANT	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:Volume:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nn>:Exchange:<-prep>:on:Volume:<-nsubj>:rose:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:issues:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/EVENT
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:district:<prep>:in:rout:<nsubj>:reminder:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:hopeful:<prep>:of:rout:<-rcmod>:backed:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<poss>:rout:<--rcmod>:backed:<-prep>:since:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:%:<nsubj>:choose:<-prep>:for:House:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:year:<prep>:in:choose:<--prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<--prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:favor:<-advmod>:more:<-prep>:in:races:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:candidacy:<pobj>:captured:<-advcl>:of:<-pobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:or:vote:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<prep>:on:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:select:<advcl>:buy:<-parataxis>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:have:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:representatives:<nsubj>:willing:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<nsubj>:hold:<advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:races:<prep>:in:voters:<nsubj>:face:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:into:put:<-conj>:but:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:put:<--conj>:but:powerless:<-xcomp>:prevent:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:races:<prep>:in:is:<-xcomp>:lean:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:election:<prep>:prior_to:occupied:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:as:[YYY]	/LAW
/LAW	[XXX]:<-dep>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<advmod>:explains:<-advcl>:hold:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-dobj>:hold:<-conj>:but:love:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:with:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:suggests:<-advcl>:have:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<xcomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:into:brought:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:placed:<advcl>:vulnerable:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/LAW
/LAW	[XXX]:<advmod>:indicates:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:have:<-dobj>:time:<-vmod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:by:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:salary:<-prep>:by:running:<-prep>:by:prospect:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/EVENT#/LAW
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:fared:<-advmod>:better:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:willing:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO	[XXX]:<dobj>:corroborate:<-ccomp>:willing:<-xcomp>:engage:<-prep>:than:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:willing:<--xcomp>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL	[XXX]:<nn>:Bennett:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Bennett:<nsubj>:find:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/LAW
/LAW	[XXX]:<advmod>:find:<--ccomp>:turn:<-dobj>:more:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<advmod>:have:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO
/CONTACT_INFO/url#/CONTACT_INFO	[XXX]:<nsubj>:valid:<advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<det>:rate:<nsubj>:exceeded:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:matter:<-acomp>:relative:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:candidates:<-prep>:in:states:<-vmod>:conducting:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:for:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:candidate:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT#/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:bill:<-rcmod>:makes:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:sent:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<xcomp>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:position:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<dep>:[YYY]	/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR
/EVENT#/EVENT/WAR	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:bill:<nsubj>:include:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE#/SUBSTANCE/FOOD	[XXX]:<amod>:funds:<-rcmod>:are:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:with:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/LAW	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<poss>:agreement:<nsubj>:make:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/LOCATION#/PERSON#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<det>:mix:<nsubj>:makes:<-xcomp>:one:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/LAW
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<prep>:in:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:Hollings:<nsubj>:attached:<-prep>:for:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<rcmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:Hollings:<-rcmod>:chairs:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:R.:<-dep>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/PERSON#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-nsubjpass>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<nsubj>:provides:<-xcomp>:meet:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:as:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<dobj>:retained:<-vmod>:advise:<-prep>:regarding:sale:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:said:<-ccomp>:extended:<-prep>:with:Securities:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<poss>:stock:<nsubj>:closed:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-tmod>:closed:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<dobj>:[YYY]	/LAW
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:spilled:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-tmod>:spilled:<-prep>:on:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:return:<-parataxis>:proposes:<-advmod>:again:<-prep>:after:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:after:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:have:<-conj>:but:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<agent>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:impound:<-conj>:or:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:users:<-conj>:but:saw:<-prep>:against:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-prep>:against:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<conj>:and:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PLANT#/ANIMAL	[XXX]:<dobj>:asking:<-xcomp>:feel:<-prep>:about:[YYY]	/PLANT#/ANIMAL
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:to:sent:<-conj>:but:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<prep>:of:%:<nsubjpass>:approved:<-agent>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<-agent>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<advcl>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<prep>:of:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:endorsed:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:voted:<-xcomp>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:told:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubj>:lurched:<-advcl>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:estimated:<-ccomp>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-nsubj>:tag:<-prep>:for:assistance:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-appos>:D.:<-dep>:Wash[YYY]	/PERSON
/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE	[XXX]:<-dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<tmod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION#/GPE#/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE
/EVENT	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/WORK_OF_ART	[XXX]:<tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/EVENT	[XXX]:<tmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:in:corporations:<prep>:of:response:<dobj>:Echoing:<dep>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-poss>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION#/PERSON	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION
/ORGANIZATION#/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nn>:crews:<nsubj>:tallied:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-dobj>:tallied:<-conj>:but:lacked:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/DISEASE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Francisco:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/FACILITY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/FACILITY/BUILDING
/FACILITY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/FACILITY/BUILDING	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:Francisco:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-conj>:and:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<nsubjpass>:shifted:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/COUNTRY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<poss>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/ORGANIZATION	[XXX]:<-dep>:said:<-ccomp>:moved:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<tmod>:met:<dep>:Committee:<nsubj>:moved:<-prep>:to:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-prep>:to:moved:<--prep>:to:Monte:<-appos>:Calif.:<-appos>:[YYY]	/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
/WORK_OF_ART#/WORK_OF_ART/SONG	[XXX]:<-appos>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/DRUG#/SUBSTANCE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<prep>:of:towns:<-prep>:near:epicenter:<-advmod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION
/LOCATION/REGION#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-advmod>:[YYY]	/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION#/WORK_OF_ART#/ORGANIZATION#/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/FACILITY#/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/FACILITY/BUILDING	[XXX]:<nn>:County:<nsubj>:has:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE
/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL#/SUBSTANCE	[XXX]:<-dobj>:[YYY]	/LOCATION
/LOCATION	[XXX]:<nsubj>:has:<-prep>:excluding:city:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/GPE/CITY#/GPE	[XXX]:<-prep>:of:[YYY]	/PERSON
/DISEASE	[XXX]:<amod>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nsubj>:uncertain:<-tmod>:[YYY]	/EVENT
/EVENT	[XXX]:<-tmod>:uncertain:<-parataxis>:collapsed:<-prep>:in:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE
/PERSON	[XXX]:<nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
/PERSON	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION
/GPE/CITY#/GPE#/LOCATION	[XXX]:<-nn>:[YYY]	/PERSON
